至4.3萬噸，去年。
Growing from 1.63 million tons of air cargo throughput.
HKIA has been the world's busiest cargo airport since 2010.
作為項目，幫助維護香港的status和競爭力，作為 premier航空樞紐。
The key drivers to Hong Kong's success as an airfreight transshipment hub of choice.
Over the past 17 years, the compound annual growth of air cargo throughput HKI is 6%.
Thank you。好啊，誒，因為啊隔離方又要投票，噉啊又要停多五分鐘。
Further development of HKIA will not only contribute to the city's economy, but will also drive job creation.
We believe a third runway is essential to maintaining the long-term competitiveness of Hong Kong.
或的優越性地圖位置、世界級效率和不 match 連接性 of the city.
In recent years, we've seen robust infrastructure development among the neighbouring airports in mainland China and other parts of Asia.
Good morning. Cathay Pacific Services Limited supports the building of the three runway system of Hong Kong International Airport.
With passenger traffic and flight movements consistently growing, we see a pressing need to speed up all infrastructure development at HKIA.
香港， on the other hand, is facing anticipated runway capacity challenge, which limits airlines' abilities to secure preferred takeoff and landing time slots.
HKIA has established an enviable international reputation since it since it opened in 1998. In view of approaching the maximum runway capacity, we see the need to enhance the city's infrastructure and build a third runway as soon as possible to maintain the hub status and competitiveness.